[The Breakfast Club
radio show plays]
It's like that, Charlamagne.
[laughing] You don't think it
kicks in immediately?
No, I don't think
it kicks in like that.
The PEDs don't kick
in immediately?
No, I don't think
it does like that.
And I don't think
it guarantees that you'll hit
a home run.
Charlamagne would do it
right before the game.
-That's right.
-No.
Now, uh, talk about
the rent in Brooklyn.
Yes, so, the average rent
in Brooklyn now
has soared up to $3,035.
Is that crazy in Brooklyn?
I don't know why anybody
would wanna live--
In the best borough?
I don't know.
For $3,000.
That's $3,000 a month?
-Yes!
-God...
You don't even get grass
in Brooklyn.
-Hell no.
-They do so have grass.
You don't have no grass
in Brooklyn.
You know what you can get
in Jersey for $3,000 a month?
That's what I'm trying
to tell him.
You know what you'd be getting
in North Carolina?
-Oh, Lord have mercy.
-Live like a king out there.
We gon' buy
Fantasia's old house.
[car engine revs]
Wake up, man!
[cars honking]
-[tires squealing]
-[crashing sound]
[distant screaming]
-[Man] Call an ambulance!
-[labored breathing]
[Man] Sir, are you okay?
[car engine revs]
Hey. Hey, stop!
Oh, my God!
-[car engine revs]
-[tires squeal]
[inaudible yelling]
[record needle drops]
♪ [Al Green's "Funny How Time
Slips Away" plays] ♪
Oh, give me a hint.
My favorite color.
Favorite color's blue.
-What?
-Blue...
Blues singer?
I can't believe you don't know
my favorite color.
-It's blue.
-No, it's green.
Well, it used to be blue.
No. Always green.
Man, what a shame.
Whatever. What's my
favorite color?
-Purple.
-Ehh.
-What?
-Lavender.
Pshht. Same thing.
Definitely not the same thing.
[laughs]
Oh, oh, oh! It's Al Green.
Don't change the subject.
You don't know
my favorite color.
Well, you changed it first.
You still haven't answered
my question about August.
We gotta book a date soon
so we can get a deal.
Yeah, August won't work.
Keith starts school.
We gotta be there
to move him in.
Mhm.
-Mm-hmm.
-What?
From foster care
to four year college.
You did that.
How's it feel?
Can't wrap my head around it.
Hmm.
Gives me the chills
and makes me wanna cry
at the same time.
Mm-hmm.
I just gotta make sure
he shows up.
He'll show up.
No, he's been through
too much not to show up.
Yeah, I hope you're right.
I am right.
-Okay? Okay.
-Okay. Okay.
Come on.
Put the cake down.
-What?
-Come here.
-What you doing?
[both] What?
-Dance with me.
-Oh.
Yeah.
-Okay.
-Oh!
Ooh, what was that?
You cannot dance like
that at our wedding.
Oh...
Once your brother moves out,
we get our apartment back.
Mhm. True.
-Our refrigerator.
-Mm-hmm.
The bathroom.
You get your car back.
-Yes, I do.
-Mm-hmm.
What?
What if we moved?
-Moved?
-It's so tight here.
Well, baby, it is New York.
Nobody has space.
Nothing big is remotely
affordable anymore.
Yeah, I can make
some more money.
With Keith gone
and the market up.
My crew's hungry.
A few more projects...
Baby, baby, baby.
Listen to me.
I don't care about more money.
Or the size of our apartment.
I'm getting married.
That's all I want.
You and me.
I'm gonna build you
a house one day.
You promise?
From my own hands.
You know how much
I love you, right?
I really do.
♪ Shining so brightly ♪
♪ It's me that's
missing your love ♪
[banging on door]
Who is that?
[banging continues]
What the...
Who is knocking like that?
[banging on door]
[loud thud]
Keith? What happened?
-[Keith sobbing]
-What happened?
Bro. What happened?
-I crashed.
-You crashed?
You crashed in my car?
Did somebody else get hurt?
They weren't moving.
No! God.
Keith, are they dead?
They're dead.
Shit!
[distant police sirens]
Keith, let me see.
I can't let this happen.
He'll be okay.
He'll be all right.
What are you doing?
Why are you putting
on his shirt?
-Chris. Stop it.
-Listen.
-Stop it!
-Li-- no.
He got a record, I don't.
-Why are you putting it on?
-I can't let this happen.
No!
-Stop it.
Stop it.
-Regardless he's going
to jail.
He did it, Chris!
You didn't do it!
You don't know
what we've been through.
What about me?
You gotta trust me, baby.
[sobbing] No, no.
[police sirens]
You can't do this.
♪ [distorted "Funny How Time
Slips Away" plays] ♪
♪ Shining so bright ♪
[muffled yelling]
[buzzer rings]
Do you have a minute?
[Woman] I need a big push,
Tara.
[Tara screams]
[Woman] Push!
-[Tara screams]
-I can see it. Push, Tara.
-That's it.
-[Tara groans]
Push!
That's it. That's it.
[baby cries]
Christopher Newborn,
the Queens, New York, man
convicted of felony
vehicular manslaughter
after a hit and run in 2011,
is being released today
after the Innocence Project
unearthed video evidence
vindicating Newborn of
an additional murder charge
stemming from a prison
fight in 2013.
Records show Newborn
served nearly
seven consecutive years
in isolation,
placed there unjustly
by guards who framed him
for the murder
of a fellow inmate.
A murder committed
by those very guards.
Now, look, I wanna deal with
the nightmare of him being
thrown
into solitary confinement
after getting framed
by these prison guards.
Seven years in the hole.
Seven.
How does that impact
this brother's mental health?
What does it mean
for his family?
How can he get his life back?
Newborn's case has not only
raised lawsuit flags,
but has launched him into the
center of the ongoing debate
over the inhumane
aspects of isolation
within the prison system.
[thunder rumbles]
[rain patters]
[thunder booms]
[buzzer rings]
[gated doors slide open]
[reporter] Just over here.
One question!
-Come on.
-[reporter] Chris, over here!
[shouting overlaps]
[reporter] Chris,
do you feel justice?
Will there be a lawsuit
against the State of New York?
[Tara laughs]
Hey, Jake, get up here.
Ready?
Lean in, everyone.
On one, two, three,
say cheese.
[camera snaps]
-Aww.
-[camera snaps]
You swipe your finger.
Like that.
All right, buckle up, Jake.
[car engine starts]
[engine revs]
[Chris] Still nothing.
[Tara] He's been better.
I mean, especially lately.
More responsive.
They say he can come out
of it. That-that he...
that he can talk.
But...
now the longer he doesn't,
the more chance he never will.
What's that thing he squeezes?
It's clay.
It's part of clay art therapy.
A doctor suggested it
a few years ago, and it stuck.
And he just squeezes it?
Sometimes, yeah.
When he's coping
or calming down.
He makes stuff too. See?
My God. He did that?
Yeah.
The way you're good at
building things,
that's how he is with clay.
Has it helped?
With the, uh, the seizures?
I think so.
That and the-the medicine.
No seizures so far this year.
[voice on TV]
Come back here!
You grew up on me.
Last time I saw you,
you were--
[Woody Woodpecker laughs on
TV]
♪ [upbeat latin music plays] ♪
[woman sings in Spanish]
♪
You used to love
to dance with me.
You were never
very good, but...
at least you tried.
If I was bad back then...
-Imagine now.
-I'm kidding.
I love the way you move.
I almost forgot.
Open it.
It's the first time
the three of us
have been in
a picture together.
Uh, Chris Newborn.
So sorry to interrupt.
Matt Walton.
Look, I heard about
what happened to you,
and I think it's just...
awful, and I think the state
should be held accountable.
Now, my firm, Bregmen,
Foss and Associates,
is both effective
and affordable--
Not interested.
Fair enough.
Well, uh...
I see you're enjoying dinner,
so I will just leave you
my card, and if you do
change your mind--
Not interested.
Chris!
We are not in danger, baby.
Think about our family,
think about Jake.
That's right.
Now breathe, baby.
Breathe.
[lights buzz]
[doorbell buzzes]
[man] You gonna let me in?
Or...
Chris, what we doin'?
I know you hear me.
Welcome home.
[Keith chuckles]
My old digs.
Memories in this place.
How'd you know I got out?
It's all they're
talking about on the news.
Video of how they
framed you is everywhere.
We always knew
you were innocent.
Didn't make no sense.
No one just snaps
and murders someone
just before release.
Saying you got a real
chance at a lawsuit.
How it could be
in the millions.
Saying how shocked they are
you survived the hole.
I wasn't surprised though.
Then again,
I know you.
Nothing can break my big bro.
Jake.
Come say hi
to your uncle Keith.
How you doing, little man?
Tara will be home
from work soon, so...
And you don't want me around
when she gets here?
I ain't ask you
to go away from me.
-You didn't have to.
-Oh, right.
'Cause that's what you do,
huh?
-Keith.
-The heroic big bro.
Flies in to save his
two-time loser brother.
Can't do this right now.
I guess I should be
saying thanks.
Stop!
Stop.
Not exactly how
I thought this would go.
I guess it is what it is.
That's my cue, huh?
All right, little man.
[door closes]
[Jake breathes heavily]
[loud thud]
Jake.
-Hey, boys.
-Tara!
T-Tara. I--
Let's get you on your side.
All right.
One, two, three.
All right, I got you.
-Is he okay?
-He's all right.
There you go.
Look at me, baby.
[Tara] Hey.
Are you okay?
[Tara] Just breathe.
All right?
How is he?
He's fine.
Just...
mostly scared.
I'm gonna ask you something.
And...
if you're not into it,
just say so.
I'll be fine with it.
How would you feel
about a trip?
-A trip?
-Yeah. Like, uh...
Like a break from the city.
Someplace that has space
and fresh air.
I--
I don't feel comfortable,
you paying for something
like that without my help.
Ella's husband.
He works real estate.
The company he's with,
they own a resort up north.
It's a quiet town.
It's already closed
for renovations.
She offered. Two weeks.
There'll be no one
there but us.
I think it could be
good for you.
good for Jake.
For us.
A trip.
♪
I'll assume you're Tara.
-Tara. Yes.
-Tara.
Ken Hershey.
Friends call me Hersh.
Chris?
You must be Big Jake.
He's not much of a talker.
You know that some of the best
men this country's ever known
were men of very few words.
Maybe while you're here,
you could be my extra
set of eyes, sorta...
like a junior
security officer.
[Tara] Hmm. Oh...
Take it.
You got a special one there.
You wanna have a look around?
Come on.
We got two wings,
connected in the lobby here.
The east wing is
the functional hotel
where you'll be.
And, uh, west Wing, you can
see is down due to a reno.
Nothing very exciting
to see there.
Let's show you to your rooms.
[ominous music plays]
Oh.
Oh, my God.
It is gorgeous.
[Hersh] Yeah. Imperial suite.
I mean, uh, it's huge.
Yeah.
You mind if I steal Chris?
Show him the rest
of the property.
Uh, of course.
Yeah. I'll-I'll get, um...
I'll get Jake settled in.
I'll show you how
everything works.
See you in a minute.
Anything you can't handle
at all, just let me know.
I'm just a mile south
down the main road.
Being out of season,
not many people around.
Wild animals?
Oh, sure. We got raccoons,
and the odd wolf. Black bear.
You probably won't see them.
They mostly mind
their own business.
So nothing too dangerous,
right?
Nothing more dangerous
than you or me.
[geese honking]
[Chris] I guess you've been
wondering where I've been
these past years.
Why I wasn't here
with you and your mom.
I made a decision.
A decision I might've...
considered differently had
I known you were on the way.
I guess,
I can't change the past,
but...
What I can do is promise you
I will never leave you again.
I will never let anything
happen to you.
I love you, son.
And your mother.
More than anything.
And I'm gonna keep doing
the best I can to prove it.
All right, uh...
Let's get through this, uh,
once and if you don't like it,
or if I'm no good at it,
just pretend to fall asleep
or something. All right?
Oh. You a comedian now.
[Jake laughs]
Do you like it here?
Yeah.
More than I thought I would.
Yeah, me too.
Reminds me
that there's a whole world
outside of the city.
Never thought I'd see the day
when the die-hard
Queens native
would entertain the idea
of leaving.
All right, I'm always
gonna be from Queens, okay?
-Okay?
-Okay.
Oh, my goodness, Jake,
this looks amazing.
Did you do this
all by yourself?
Look at you.
What's wrong, baby?
I don't know.
Um...
Oh... it's okay,
it's okay, it's okay.
You're okay.
It's okay. Okay?
-Yeah.
-Look at me.
-You're with me, it's okay.
Okay.
Okay, baby.
-Okay.
-I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Don't be sorry.
-I'm sorry.
-No.
No, no, no, no,
don't be sorry.
This is not your fault.
We can...
We can, we can wait.
Until you're ready.
It's just...
been a long time.
I know.
Have you, uh...
thought-thought
at all about the...
the lawsuit?
-Lawsuit?
-Yeah, against, um, the state.
The Bureau of Prisons.
What-what they did
to you, baby,
what they did to you was,
it's not right to our family.
It is not right.
Someone needs
to be held accountable.
And if it's, if it's true,
what they're saying,
that there could be
a settlement, that could--
that could mean a new life.
It could mean
more support for Jake.
Give him the best chance
at the best treatment.
Could--
Could get us all
the help we need.
I-I wouldn't, I wouldn't
know where to begin.
Okay, baby, that's okay.
I can do some research.
You know, I could, I could
see what our options are.
Okay.
-Okay?
-Yeah. Okay.
[muffled yelling]
[lights buzz]
Hello?
[breathing heavily]
[car horn honks]
-[Tara laughs]
-[indistinct conversation]
-[Hersh] Yeah.
[both] Hey.
Hey.
Yeah, I brought you
some goodies.
Some veggies from the garden.
Where's Jake?
Uh, inside.
You, uh, settling in okay?
Yeah. Just fine.
Well, you chose a beautiful
day for a jog.
All right, I'm gonna head out.
Finish binge-watching Ozark.
If you need me, I'm just--
A mile south on the main road.
Yeah, we know.
All right.
-[Tara] Thanks.
-You bet.
[truck engine starts]
[truck pulls away]
That was rude.
There's something about him.
I don't know.
Let me know when
he comes around, okay?
Yeah. Okay.
[muffled yelling]
I got a letter from your mom
when you turned five.
They'd been blocking
my mail for years.
But this one got through.
She said you still
hadn't spoke yet.
And I knew that was on me.
The world being what it is,
if I had just
been there for you,
maybe things would've
been different.
You're my mission.
You know that?
From now on, we face
the world together, aight?
Did you just give me
a direct answer?
Two years in, days from
release, you intervene
as guards
beat a man to death.
This is video that has been
widely circulated
which proves you acted
in self-defense.
If those men didn't
frame you, Chris,
you would've been headed home
to be with your family.
Instead, you get
a life sentence.
Worse, to hide their crimes,
they bury you in solitary
confinement to be forgotten.
No visitation, no programs.
Seven years of hell.
Those are the details.
Details that will give
the court just a small idea
of the tragedy
that you've endured.
[buzzer rings]
[steel doors slide open]
[men yelling]
I'm ready to kill
somebody today!
You think you can touch me?
Come get me!
You cannot come in here!
Come get me! Come!
[stapler gun clacks]
[saw buzzes]
[sander grinding]
[vehicle approaches]
[vehicle door opens and
closes]
[vehicle drives off]
What the hell
are you doing here?
Great to see you, too.
Who brought you here?
You need to call him back.
What is this, déjà vu?
Of course you're high.
Come on, get inside.
-[loud thud]
-[gasps]
No suite?
Whoever brought you here,
you need to call him
to come get you.
You at all curious
how this happened?
Something to do with
the needle marks on your arm?
Someone came looking for you.
Day after I saw you.
-Looking for me?
-Two guys.
They knew I was your brother.
Looked like they could've
been law enforcement.
Asked questions about you.
Me.
-Our family.
-What'd you tell 'em?
It would've been worse,
but I ran.
How'd you know I was here?
Tara told the neighbor
across the hall.
In case of emergency.
These guys...
I think they had something
to do with your case.
Hey, son.
What you doing here,
you can't sleep?
Uncle Keith may stay here
for a few days.
Uh... he's sick,
and we're gonna
look after him, aight?
What up, nephew?
Probably best we don't tell
your mom about this.
I got a feeling he's not
the snitching type.
She might not think he's
the best influence on you.
Come on, let's head back.
Chris.
No matter what happens,
just keep Jake safe.
Safe from who?
Everyone.
Your Uncle Keith,
he was the type of kid
that after he watched
a superhero movie,
he became that character.
Superpowers and all.
This one time,
he's like... six.
We're home alone
watching Spider-Man.
And within five minutes,
he's climbing the walls.
So, I'm thinking...
he's occupied.
So, I started doing
my homework.
Little did I know,
that this genius has
unplugged the cable cord,
and tied it to this huge
"if you touch it,
we will kill you"
china cabinet.
Nuh-uh. [laughs]
So, I'm studying or whatever,
and I hear what sounds like
a truck crashing
in the front room.
So, I run in there,
and here's Keith.
Spider-Man underwear on,
stocking over his head,
standing over this
collapsed china cabinet
and broken glass everywhere.
Oh, no.
-It gets worse.
-Nuh-uh.
It gets worse.
At exactly that moment,
our foster parents' car
pulls up in the driveway.
Oh, God.
What did you do?
Would any sensible
11 year old would do.
I knocked some pictures
off the wall,
told 'em it was
an earthquake.
[laughs] In Brooklyn.
Made sense in my head.
But, yeah.
We didn't last much longer
with that family.
[phone buzzes and pings]
You good?
Yeah. [laughs]
I'm gonna use the ladies room.
Don't get any ideas
from your father.
[Tara chuckles]
[door bell rings]
Hey, Jake. Come on.
Hey!
[ticking sound]
[muted dialogue]
[men yelling]
[yelling intensifies]
[police radio chatter]
I got a call.
From Ella.
She needed to talk.
I shouldn't have left you,
I just--
I'm sorry.
Hersh.
How'd he know we were here?
I called him.
You have his number?
He gave it to us both, Cris.
They would've arrested you.
I--
I figured he could help.
Change of clothes.
What you mean by
what you said last night?
About keeping Jake safe?
The guys who came
looking for you.
They asked about you.
And Jake.
But they never asked
where you were.
They just told me
to stay away from you.
That they wanted you
to be alone.
Isolated.
Vulnerable.
That's why I knew
I had to come find you.
So whatever they were
coming at you with,
you wouldn't have to
face 'em alone.
I had a dream I OD'd.
I'm tired of this ride, bro.
I'm ready to get off.
Hey.
-Mmm.
-Where are you?
What did I do?
I feel, I feel so alone here.
Let the two of us on,
on two separate trips.
I know. Hey, I know, I know.
I know there's
a lot that you're
still trying to figure out.
And I don't wanna
get in the way of that.
What do you want?
Your love.
That's all.
Do you love me still?
Yeah.
I love you.
Yeah, okay.
Okay.
[crickets chirping]
[seagull caws]
[buzzer rings]
[muffled announcement]
If you've seen it
in your mind,
you can create it
and you can get there
from right here.
Protect your mind, son.
It's your greatest asset.
Hey.
You don't let nobody walk
through it with dirty feet.
You hear me?
Protect your mind.
-[gunshot]
-[bullet whizzes by]
We're here.
Stay close.
Your life just got spared,
sir.
Man, I don't know how
it works in the city, but...
trespassing around here
usually ends with
a pine box and nails.
We got shot at today.
You get shot at
in these woods here?
Yeah.
-In these woods?
-In these woods.
This afternoon.
Well, that's odd,
Chris, 'cause...
not many people
around here.
Nobody hunts
around here but me.
And were you hunting?
This afternoon?
Come on, Jake.
I'm not sure how it
works in the country,
but in the city,
when someone shoots at you,
you don't wait for it
to happen again.
Hey.
You be careful out there.
You too.
Can I help you?
Yeah, yeah. Uh...
my son here.
His first season.
Uh, looking for a rifle.
Summer hunting or fall?
What's-what's the difference?
Oh, just the game. Uh...
maybe the caliber.
We got red squirrels,
sparrows, starlings,
rock pigeons,
monk parakeets.
Of course, come fall,
you got everything else.
We're going to be hunting
bigger game, so, uh...
I'd say fall.
Deer or bear?
Yeah. Uh... deer.
Okay, well,
then you're probably looking
for a mid-size caliber.
That is a, uh, Browning
A-Bolt, extended barrel.
You can hit a buck
a hundred yards away.
Barely no slope.
Yeah, I'll take it.
Uh... good deal.
Uh, I'm gonna need to see
some ID and a game license.
Oh...
You didn't grab Daddy's wallet
off the counter, did you?
Oh, man.
Um.
You know what?
My wife's card.
I used it to grab some
groceries this morning.
Maybe I could use this
for now?
Bring back my paperwork
in the next day or so?
You don't have no ID.
You don't have a game license
or a money card
with your name on it.
And you want me to let you
walk outta here with a rifle?
Let's get you in the car.
If they're here,
that mean we all
in danger, right?
Maybe we tell Tara I'm here.
Pissed as she might be,
at least I'll be on
that side with you.
I'm not scared.
I'm just saying.
Or maybe we call the cops.
Cops?
[scoffs]
Don't think Hersh
knows 'em all by name?
Don't be afraid, son.
I won't let anything
happen to you.
Load that up.
[gun cocks]
Something happens to me...
it's gonna be just you
to take care of your mom.
You see it?
Breathe.
Pull the trigger.
Pull it.
-Jake.
-[trigger clicks]
You did it.
Courage under stress.
Very good.
Proud of you, son.
[branch snaps]
[leaves rustle]
Get behind me.
Get down, get down.
You got three seconds
to come out!
Three.
Two.
One!
[gunshot]
Jake!
[wolf snarls]
[snarls]
[snarls and barks]
Jake.
Don't move.
Stay where you are, Jake.
[flesh squishing]
Ahh!
[wolf whines]
[Chris gasps loudly]
What happened?
What happened, Chris?
Chris, what happened?
Come on. Okay, sit.
Sit, sit, sit, sit.
Okay, okay, okay.
Okay, baby.
Jake, go to the bathroom.
Go get my first aid kit,
uh, the toiletry kit.
And some towels please.
Baby, what happened?
What happened, baby?
Tell me what happened.
-[Tara] Lift up.
-[Chris groans]
Someone was out there.
Before we got attacked.
Watching us.
Are you sure it wasn't...
just someone in the woods?
Hiking,
like you and Jake were.
Yeah, I'm sure.
I yelled for 'em
to come out, they hid.
Maybe they were afraid.
Why would they be afraid
of a guy and his kid walking?
Well,
you said you were yelling.
'Cause they were following us.
Well, how do you know
they weren't just--
Why are you so convinced
I didn't see what I saw?
You're all done.
I'm gonna go wash up.
[muffled yelling]
Help me get outta here,
please!
Please! It's not right!
Please help me get outta here!
Please don't leave me.
Don't leave me!
[Reporter] A developing system
is moving in tonight
from the west,
bringing increasing cloud
cover and rising pressure
across the region.
Skies will darken through
the early morning hours
as that system
continues to build.
Winds are expected
to pick up gradually.
Steady at first,
then shifting direction
as the front begins
to organize.
By midday tomorrow,
scattered thunder is likely,
with a chance
of more sustained activity
into the evening.
-Hey.
-Hey. Morning.
[TV shuts off]
Can I help you?
Oh, just doing my rounds,
checking on things.
There's no one here but us.
Yeah, I heard there was
some gunshots let off
in the woods around here.
You asking if it was me?
No, I already know
the answer to that one.
Wondering more what it means.
I'm still not sure what
all of this has to do with me.
Really?
You're not the first
to travel this road.
You don't have to do it alone.
You're trying
to get in my head.
I'm trying to offer you
some grace here, man.
Who are you to give me grace?
-A friend?
-A friend.
When did that happen?
Maybe when some weapons
went missing
in the gun shop parking lot.
Or the dead wolf.
Or the-the trail of blood.
I'd appreciate it if you
didn't come by anymore.
Not while we're still here.
[Keith] You think he's
connected to the case?
[Chris] I don't know.
Trying to put it all together.
[Keith] What about Tara?
It was her idea
to bring you out here.
She got the ball rolling
on the settlement.
Between her and Hersh...
I'm just saying.
Gotta keep our eyes open.
Keep Jake close.
[whispering]
Chris?
[door opens and closes]
You're up.
I'm up.
So, when's the, um,
big reveal?
For
that thing you're building.
There's nothing to reveal.
I'm just building.
Really.
Well, um...
I'd-I'd still like to see
what you've been
so secretive about.
It's no secret.
It's just a workspace.
Just a place I can be alone.
That's it. Just like a...
like a, like a man cave.
A cave?
Or cell?
Chris, tha--
that is not normal.
That space was all I had here.
That's not true.
The only safe space...
I had here.
And you--
you took that away.
You're not in prison
anymore, Chris.
You are not there anymore.
You are here.
You are here with me and Jake
and your family who loves you.
You had no right!
[door slams]
[keyboard tapping]
I'm thinking of...
heading into town.
[cartoons play on TV]
Jake's outta clay.
And we can use
a few other things too.
You mind, uh...
you mind if
I take Jake with me?
You don't need my permission.
We shouldn't be too long.
Have you seen my phone?
It was charging this morning.
Before our talk.
No. I haven't.
I respect other
people's things.
Okay. Come on.
Let's get you buckled. Okay?
Okay.
[air hissing]
Come on, baby.
Let's go.
All right.
Okay, you see
Daddy coming, you knock.
Real hard, yeah?
All right.
You good?
Okay, I love you.
[phone chimes]
The car has a flat.
The spare's flat too.
I was thinking maybe...
maybe Instacarting something,
but the Internet is down.
It's fine.
Yeah, uh, we can go tomorrow.
Yeah?
Come here, Jake.
Come on.
Let's get ready for bed.
Yeah?
Maybe get some ice cream.
Looks like he's okay
here with me.
Yeah. Okay.
[Chris] It's bad, bro.
It's all bad.
And Tara?
I think she's...
We aight.
We good, we good.
[Keith] The settlement.
-[Tara] Okay.
-The millions.
-[call dialing]
-Okay.
-[call rings]
-Come on.
It's why they let you out.
It's the reason
she lured you here.
[Man] 911.
What's your emergency?
[Keith] Reason they're
planning to take Jake.
[Man] 911.
What's your emergency?
[Man] Hello?
Is anybody there?
[Keith] They had the place.
They had the plan.
[Keith] And with Hersh, a vet,
they had the perfect
set of eyes.
[voicemail beeps]
You have two new messages.
Hello, this is Dr. Salinas,
resident psychiatrist
at Western State
Correctional Facility.
I received your message
regarding Christopher Newborn
and was deeply troubled.
Tara was the last piece.
She found a perfect place,
and even a lawyer
to start the paperwork.
She just had to play her part.
The money gets split
three ways.
[Dr. Salinas] There are
a few things you should know.
Things you should've
been told
before he ever
left the facility.
Everything you thought
about it was true.
You knew it all along.
We knew it all along.
[call rings]
Hi, Dr. Salinas.
It's Tara Bishop.
I called you earlier.
I just got your message.
No, no. No, I'm alone.
He's inside with my son.
And there's something else.
I told you I hadn't
talked to Tara
since the night
you went away.
That's not true.
Yeah, but--
What are you saying?
Well...
Tara...
and...
and I, we...
Me and her...
I didn't plan on it.
Neither of us did.
But...
It happened.
A couple times.
Then a lot more.
Oh--
[Keith] It was a mistake.
But you don't need her, bro.
You got me.
You got Jake.
Tara.
She's just a whore.
A lyin',
plottin',
disloyal,
opportunist--
-[crashing sound]
-[men groan]
-[groaning]
-[punch lands]
-[bone snaps]
-[Chris screams]
[fighting noises]
[yelling]
I gave my life for you!
Nine years!
For what you did!
You come over here, Jake.
-Come on over here.
-Jake, don't move!
Hey!
You stay put.
Jake! Come here.
That's your plan all along?
Try to take my son from me?
Jake, you come over here
with me, it's okay.
Jake. Come here.
Now.
Come with me.
-[gunshot]
-[loud thud]
He tried to take Jake!
Your plan won't work.
-Chris...
-It's not gonna work!
Okay.
[Tara] Okay.
Baby.
Chris.
Put the gun down,
baby, please.
No one is trying to take Jake.
You didn't think he'd
find out what you did?
-Chris.
-Answer him.
-Please.
-She's still in it.
-Tara.
-Okay, Jake--
Don't!
Baby, listen to me.
Okay?
I spoke to Dr. Salinas.
What?
Shoot her.
She told me what you were
going through.
About Keith.
Shoot her.
Keith told me everything
about you and him.
-Chris.
-He's been here with me
the whole time.
Keith died of an overdose.
New Year's Eve,
seven years ago.
-Chris.
-I wrote you a letter.
You wrote back.
No.
You had me file a grievance to
release you for the funeral.
-They denied it.
-No.
Try to remember, baby, please.
No, I went in
to save him.
-To protect him.
-You did.
You gave him a second chance
and he relapsed.
Chris, she's trying
to get in your head.
-Shoot this lying bitch.
-Stop!
Stop.
Keith?
[whimpers]
Oh, baby.
-Baby.
-He was-- [whimpers]
[breathing heavily]
Keith!
Hey, Jake.
Say hi to your uncle Keith.
And we're gonna
look after him, right?
Probably best we don't
mention this to your mom.
You got three seconds
to come out!
Three. Two.
-One.
-[gunshot]
[muffled screaming]
I gave my life for you!
Okay.
Jake.
Baby.
Okay.
Okay. Okay.
Keith?
They're gonna come, bro.
And they're gonna take him.
You can't let that happen.
-[Keith] Chris.
-Chris.
-[Keith] Get up.
-Get up.
-[Keith] Get up, Chris.
-Get up, Chris.
[both] Go get your son.
[Chris] Tara!
Jake?
[gasps]
[groans]
[tapping sound]
[tapping continues]
Okay, baby. Let's go.
Let's go.
[groans]
[muffled radio chatter]
Rangers. Over.
This is Hersh.
I've been shot.
Got a family in trouble here.
I need you up here quick.
Jake?
Tara!
Okay.
Okay, you're okay.
Okay. Relax, I got you.
I got you. I got you.
Okay, let's lie down.
Okay.
Okay, baby.
Hi.
You okay?
You're okay.
[whispering]
You're okay. We're okay.
We're okay.
We're okay, we're okay.
[Chris] Tara.
Open the door.
Look, you're free to go.
All right?
You're free to go.
You can do whatever you want
with whoever.
But you can't keep
my son from me.
Tara!
-[pounds on the door]
-Open the door.
[pounding continues]
Stop it, Chris.
Tara.
[Chris groans]
Okay, it's okay. You're okay.
You're okay.
You're okay, you're okay.
[thumping]
What...
What happened to me?
Tara.
I-I think I'm sick.
Baby. I'm sick.
I'm sick.
I thought I could make
things right again.
I thought I could
put behind me
what they--
what they did to me.
What they took from me.
But I'm sick.
I'm sorry.
For what I've caused you.
And Jake.
Son, you hear me?
I love you, son.
[distant police sirens]
[Chris] Oh, no.
Jake!
Jake, listen to your mom.
Aight?
You listen to your mom,
always.
You protect
her with your life.
Tara.
I love you.
I love you so much.
Baby.
♪
Baby?
Chris?
[Officer] Drop the gun!
[muffled yelling]
[Officer] I see it.
On the ground!
[Officer] Put
the gun down now!
[muffled yells]
[Keith] They're gonna
take you back.
And this time...
It'll be forever.
You'll die in here.
In the hole.
Alone.
[distorted] Put the gun down!
Put it down!
Dad!
[gun clatters]
[birds chirping softly]
[indistinct conversation]
Hey.
[Chris] Thank you.
What's up, Dad?
Hey, son.
So, today's the day.
Yes, it is.
Are you okay?
Can I get you anything?
I got everything I need.
I got you.
Come on.
Let's go home.
♪
[vocalizing]
♪ Speak to me ♪
♪ Peace of me ♪
♪ I need peace ♪
[vocalizing]
♪
♪ Me ♪
[vocalizing]
♪ Trace the light ♪
♪ Fear excites ♪
♪ Shadows of fear ♪
♪ Poison... ♪
♪
♪ I was never scared
to be alone ♪
♪ But this loneliness
will put you in a zone ♪
♪ Say you checkin' on me,
you ain't even come ♪
♪ A word might be all I need
to get it done ♪
♪ I get dropped in the water
and a nigga grow fins ♪
♪ Talking 'bout you sorry,
you ain't talkin' bout shit ♪
♪ Once a lotta life,
I can't never... ♪
♪ Effort like it's pressure ♪
♪ Ain't a storm
that I can weather ♪
♪ Speak to me ♪
♪